Dad, you're going to have to come home early today.
My mom's not answering her phone. But this asshole crashed this thing. This one had diarrhea. This one.
I have diarrhea.
On the ground
In a cage on the carpet
Leave now, now, now. I can't leave now. Dad doesn't get home until 6:00.
Do it as soon as possible.
Okay. I'm not answering my mom's phone as soon as I can.
My mom isn't answering her phone.
Leave it alone. Don't clean it up, it stinks.
No, I don't smell it yet, but I'm gonna have to wipe it down a little bit. Some of the chunks are coming out, and it's a big puddle. Now.
So you two are sick.
I think I ate something wrong with this thing. I'm looking at it now and it's now 50,000 poop bags. This motherfucker.
He's got it all on his quilt.
I just got home.
어
I'll be right there.
Hurry up. I get off work at 5:30.
Okay, I'll be there as soon as I can.
I can't watch that right now. I don't want to eat anything right now. I'm hungry.
So, are you going to Grandma's?
No I don't want to bother
Okay. Okay.
That would be a bed.
Okay, okay.
Come on.